
Question: "The piece of plastic covering the ends of your shoelace, so you don’t have to moisten them with spit to thread them through your shoelace holes."
Answer: "Aglet"

Question: "The posts in the parking lot let that lets wheelchairs and shopping carts go through, but not your car."
Answer: "Bollard"

Question: "Non-alphanumeric, non-punctuation characters, usually used when you want to write something that you don’t want your children to read."
Answer: "Dingbat"

Question: "The metal band that connects the pencil eraser to the end of the pencil."
Answer: "Ferrule"

Question: "The leather loop in your belt or watch strap that keeps the end in place after it has been fastened through the buckle."
Answer: "Keeper"

Question: "The groove made by a sawblade, ie, the width of a cut. In the image above we see a 2.5 micron kerf."
Answer: "Kerf"

Question: "The small indentation at the bottom or a wine bottle, designed to give the bottle extra strength, and also, to make it look like it has more wine than it really does."
Answer: "Punt"
Answer: "Kick"

Question: "The vertical groove between your lip and nose that separates your left and right mustache, unless you’re Hitler, then it’s the part that your mustache covers."
Answer: "Philtrum"

Question: "The points of light that you see behind your eyelids when you shut your eyes really hard."
Answer: "Phosphenes"

Question: "The little piece of cartilage that sticks out at the front side of your ear."
Answer: "Tragus"